Okay, in the last video, we proved that
you could in fact store a function in a
variable. So, let's see what you can do
with that. Uh, to do that, I'm going to
create another function here, and I'm
going to call it display type. And it's
going to take in
an input value as input,
and then it's going to return the type
of the input value.
Then down here, I'm going to create a
variable called my var. And I'm going to
set it equal to a string.
And then I'm going to create a variable
called result and set it equal to the
result of calling display type and
giving it the input of my var. And then
once that's done, I'm going to alert the
result. Okay. So what this should do is
if it works correctly, we should take my
var. We should give it to display type.
It will then store that in input value.
So now input value should be resto
should be storing hello. So then when we
return the type of input value, it
should return that this is a string and
alert it. So let's save that
and let's come to our code and it says
string. Hooray. Okay, let's come back
here. Let's change this to a three.
We'll save it and it says it's a number.
Cool. Let's change it to the word true.
Save it. Come back over. It's a boolean.
Okay. Well, we know now that you can
take a function and I'm going to
uncomment the function we wrote in the
last video and we can store it
in a variable. So now what I'm going to
do is I'm going to call uh I'm going to
pass that variable that we created
called my function into display type and
we'll see what we get. So now it says
that the type of variable that we got
inside the function is a function which
is great because that means that if we
can store a function in a variable it
means we can pass that function into
another function as a piece of input.
Now why would you want to do this? Well,
that's a topic for the next